profsl.com 2018-07-21

# Privacy Policy

**ProFSL.com Privacy Policy**

ProFSL, LLC (hereinafter, also referred to as ‘We’ or ‘Website’ or ‘Our’ or ‘Us’ and similar derivatives) accords highest priority to protecting the online privacy of its users (hereinafter, also referred to as ‘You’ or ‘Your’ and similar derivatives). 

This Privacy Policy (hereinafter, also referred to as ‘Policy’) will inform You about the nature of information We collect; and how We use, protect, and sometimes, disclose such information.

 **Amendments and Updates**  
This Policy or any part hereof is subject to amendments, updates and/or changes at any time without any prior notice to anyone. All such modifications shall come into effect immediately upon posting. You are advised to visit this page periodically for latest on Privacy Policy.

 _Last Updated on: November 1st, 2011_

 **Privacy of Children**  
We comply with the principles and provisions of Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children below the age of 13 years.  If you are under 13 years of age, you are expressly prohibited from using our web site by our Terms of Use , which is incorporated herein by reference.  In the event that We have inadvertently collected any personal information from a child below 13 years of age, We encourage Our users to bring to Our attention all such instances. We shall take all reasonable steps to delete such information from Our servers.

 **Collection and Use of Personal Information**  
We collect some personally identifiable information from the users during registration process or when purchasing a product.  Such information includes, but is not limited to, Your name, email address, place of residence, billing address, phone number, and gender. Only that much personal information is collected as is absolutely vital to provide you efficient and timely services. All such personal information is kept confidential and not shared with, or sold to, or traded with, any third party. 

**Opt-in and Opt-Out:** We only send the alerts, newsletter, latest offers, news, and updates to users who opt-in to receive such alerts.  If You no longer want to receive alerts, You can always change these settings in your user account after logging into the website with your account name and password. 

You may receive mails or emails from Us carrying information on new products and/or services and/or upcoming events. If You do not wish to receive such mails or emails, please let Us know by sending e-mail at [admin@profsl.com](mailto:admin@profsl.com).  If You are receiving automated notifications from ProFSL.com, and You do not wish to receive such emails, please update your [notification settings](http://www.profsl.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;area=notification) in your profile.

  **Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information**  
In addition to the above-mentioned personally identifiable information, when You visit different pages on this Website, We may also collect certain non-personal information as well including, but not limited to, the type of browser used to access this Website, Internet Protocol (IP) Address of Your computer, IP address of your Internet Service Provider (ISP), the Operating System installed on your computer, etc.  We may collect this information directly, or use a third party to collect this information on our behalf.  Generally, this information is used to improve the layout and content of this Website, provide You with customized advertisements, analyze the Website usage, and enhance Your overall website-usage experience. All such non-personal information is kept confidential and not shared with, or sold to, any third party.

 **Collection and Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are small text files that are placed on the hard disk of Your computer system by a Web page server. The cookies are employed to determine information, like how You use Our site, how You use Our services, etc. The cookies are also used to remember the repeat visitors without any requirement to login repeatedly while the session is on. Our cookies do not compromise Your online privacy or damage Your computer system in any manner whatsoever.

 **Third Party Links**  
This Website may also contain links to third-party websites of promoters, advertisers, affiliates, partners, agents, etc. However, We do not review, control or monitor the privacy practices of such linked third party websites. We recommend acquaintance with the policies and procedures of the linked websites before interacting with them.

 **Disclosure of Information**  
Our use of Your personal and non-personal information is strictly in accordance with the policies and provisions outlined hereinabove, except:

1.   Disclosure to government agencies in response to legal processes, like subpoena etc.; or  
2.   Any unlawful or unauthorized access to and transmissions of information from this Website; or  
3.   Disclosure of any information by You on Message Boards, Public Forums, Blogs, Social Networking Websites, etc. or any other publicly accessible online or offline media; or   
4.   Disclosure of such information as an asset on account of sale, or part sale, of this Website to a third party.

 **OWNERSHIP AND USE OF POSTED INFORMATION**  
Any communication or material (including any information, data, communications, software, photos, video, graphics, music, sounds, and other materials that can be viewed on a website) that you transmit to this site or to us, whether by electronic mail, post, or other means, for the purpose of public consumption on the internet, will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary. While you retain all rights in such communications or material, you grant us and our agents and affiliates a non-exclusive, paid-up, perpetual, and worldwide right to copy, distribute, display, perform, publish, translate, adapt, modify, and otherwise use such material (including material submitted prior to the effective date of this Policy) for any commercial or non-commercial purpose regardless of the form or medium (now known, not currently known, or not yet devised) in which it is used.  Additional terms relating to transmitted communications or materials are found in our [Terms of Use](http://www.profsl.com/smf/index.php?page=termsofuse) .
